(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
迫るショッカー 地獄の軍団
Approaching Shocker, the legion of hell
我らを狙う 黒い影
Black shadows aiming at us
世界の平和を 守るため
To protect the world's peace
ゴーゴー・レッツゴー 輝くマシン
Go go let's go, shining machine
ライダー (ジャンプ!)
Rider (Jump!)
ライダー (キック!)
Rider (Kick!)
仮面ライダー 仮面ライダー
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
ライダー ライダー
Rider, Rider
ライダー (ジャンプ!)
Rider (Jump!)
ライダー (キック!)
Rider (Kick!)
仮面ライダー 仮面ライダー
Kamen Rider, Kamen Rider
ライダー ライダー
Rider, Rider
第１話 ヒーロー爆誕！？ 雪花ラミィの旅立ち！
Ep 1: A Hero is Born!? Lamy's Departure!
あーっつ！
Hot!!
いや、火薬の量間違えて爆発させすぎちゃったよ
No, I messed up the gunpowder and overdid it.
もう、せっかくの眉毛が燃えちゃうよ
Geez, my precious eyebrows will burn off.
あっ、雪民さん！ありがとう！
Ah, Yukimi-san! Thank you!
おー！みんな！今日は来てくれてありがとう！
Oh! Everyone! Thank you for coming today!
そうです、今日はラミィの誕生日です！
That's right, today is Lamy's birthday!
そして、今年のラミィは一味違います！
And this year, Lamy is a little different!
今年も体力づくりで力をつけてきたけど
I've been building up my strength this year...
みんな知ってる？なんでラミィが頑張ってたか
but do you know why I was working so hard?
実はね、ヒーローになるためなんだー！
Actually, it's to become a hero!
でも、ヒーローって言ってもいろんな形があるじゃん？
But heroes come in many different forms, right?
だから今日は自分だけのヒーロー像を
So today, I'm setting out on a journey
探す旅に出ようと思いまーーす！
to find my own ideal of a hero!
ん？なんだい？
Hmm? What is it?
や、やめろー！
S-stop it!
おりゃー！
Orya!
雪民さん！
Yukimi-san!
ラミィを守ってくれたの？
Did you protect Lamy?
さっきもバイク片付けてくれたし
You even put away the bike earlier...
雪民さんは本当にえらいねー！
Yukimi-san, you're really great!
よしよしよしよし
There, there, there, there.
あ、だいふくもいたの？
Ah, Daifuku was here too?
ちょっとまた敵が来ないか見張っといて
Keep a lookout in case more enemies come.
今日はね、いろんなゲストを呼んで
Today, we invited various guests
たくさんのヒーローを見ることができるから楽しみだね！
to see many heroes, so I'm excited!
それじゃあ雪花ラミィ、ヒーロー探しの旅に行ってきまーす！
Well then, I'm off on my hero-finding journey!
なんで... なんでまた雪民ばかり...
Why... why is it always Yukimi...
僕だって... 僕だって...
I also... I also...
ガチャモンの歌
Gachamon's Song
ガチャモン ガチャモン
Gachamon Gachamon
ガッチャマンの歌
Gatchaman no Uta
だれだ だれだ だれだ
Who is it, who is it, who is it
空の彼方に踊る影
A shadow dancing in the distance of the sky
白い翼のガッチャマン
It's the white-winged Gatchaman
命をかけて飛び出せば
If he leaps out, risking his life
科学忍法 火の鳥だ
It's the Science Ninja Technique: Firebird
飛べ 飛べ 飛べ ガッチャマン
Fly, fly, fly, Gatchaman
行け 行け 行け ガッチャマン
Go, go, go, Gatchaman
地球は一つ 地球は一つ
The Earth is one, the Earth is one
おお ガッチャマン ガッチャマン
Oh, Gatchaman, Gatchaman
だれだ だれだ だれだ
Who is it, who is it, who is it
海の地獄に潜む影
A shadow lurking in the hell of the sea
強い勇気のガッチャマン
It's the Gatchaman of strong courage
嵐を裂いて雲切れば
If he splits the storm and cuts the clouds
科学忍法 火の鳥だ
It's the Science Ninja Technique: Firebird
飛べ 飛べ 飛べ ガッチャマン
Fly, fly, fly, Gatchaman
行け 行け 行け ガッチャマン
Go, go, go, Gatchaman
地球は一つ 地球は一つ
The Earth is one, the Earth is one
おお ガッチャマン ガッチャマン
Oh, Gatchaman, Gatchaman
だれだ だれだ だれだ
Who is it, who is it, who is it
ビルの谷間に忍ぶ影
A shadow sneaking in the canyons of buildings
赤い血潮のガッチャマン
It's the red-blooded Gatchaman
夕日を浴びて駆け出せば
If he runs out bathed in the setting sun
科学忍法 火の鳥だ
It's the Science Ninja Technique: Firebird
飛べ 飛べ 飛べ ガッチャマン
Fly, fly, fly, Gatchaman
行け 行け 行け ガッチャマン
Go, go, go, Gatchaman
地球は一つ 地球は一つ
The Earth is one, the Earth is one
おお ガッチャマン ガッチャマン
Oh, Gatchaman, Gatchaman
キン肉マン Go Fight!
Kinnikuman Go Fight!
ハッ ハッ
Ha! Ha!
Go! Go! Muscle!
リングに 稲妻走り
Lightning flashes in the ring
炎の戦士をてらす
Illuminating the warrior of flames
飛び散れ キン肉ビーム
Muscle beams scatter
勝利に向かって
Heading towards victory
私は (ドジで) 強い (つもり)
I'm (clumsy but) strong (in my mind)
キン肉マン
Kinnikuman
走る (すべる) 見事に (ころぶ)
Running (slipping) and brilliantly (falling)
ああ 心に愛がなければ
Ah, if there is no love in your heart
スーパーヒーローじゃないのさ
You are not a superhero
キン肉マン Go Fight!
Kinnikuman Go Fight!
ハッ ハッ
Ha! Ha!
Go! Go! Muscle!
嵐の必殺技で
With a storm of finishing moves
けちらす超人レスラー
Scattering the superhuman wrestlers
マットに真っ赤な薔薇が
A crimson rose on the mat
今夜も咲くのさ
Will bloom again tonight
私は (ドジで) 強い (つもり)
I'm (clumsy but) strong (in my mind)
キン肉マン
Kinnikuman
誰もが (誰も) 待って (いない)
Everyone (No one) is waiting (not)
ああ 果てない夢を追いかけ
Ah, chasing an endless dream
ああ 果てない夢を追いかけ (Uh~ Uh~ Uh~ Uh~)
Ah, chasing an endless dream (Uh~ Uh~ Uh~ Uh~)
スーパーヒーローになるのさ (Ha~)
I'm going to become a superhero (Ha~)
キン肉マン Go Fight!
Kinnikuman Go Fight!
私は (ドジで) 強い (つもり)
I am (clumsy) but (I think I'm) strong
キン肉マン
Kinnikuman
走る (すべる) 見事に (ころぶ)
Running (slipping) and falling (spectacularly)
ああ 心に愛がなければ (Uh~ Uh~ Uh~ Uh~)
Ah, if there's no love in your heart (Uh~ Uh~ Uh~ Uh~)
スーパーヒーローじゃないのさ (Ha~)
You're not a superhero (Ha~)
キン肉マン Go Fight!
Kinnikuman Go Fight!
ホロレンジャー 生誕3Dヒーローショー
Holo Rangers: Birthday 3D Hero Show
微か仄日
Kasuka Sokujitsu
聞こえないように 俯く体を
A body looking down so as not to be heard
誰か包んで…壊れる前に
Someone, embrace it... before it breaks
弾き出し嘲笑い 瞳を打つ
Repelling, mocking, hitting the eyes
翳への引き金
The trigger toward the shadows
踏み込む強さより 抗う痛みなら
Rather than the strength to step in, if it's the pain of resisting
誰より前で 食らう Conscience
Consuming conscience ahead of everyone else
引き千切られたプライドが 心に巻くブリザード
Torn pride wraps a blizzard around the heart
ねえ ここから出してよって 叫んでないの？
Hey, aren't you screaming "Get me out of here"?
埋もれた声は低い空が いつも救ってくれたね
The low sky always saved the buried voices, didn't it?
砕かれた幻想の果て でもまだ終わらせない
At the end of shattered illusions, I won't let it end yet
My heart will doubt...?
悲しみ宿った 花びらに伝う
Streaming down petals where sadness dwells
涙が落ちた 儚き結晶
Tears fell, fleeting crystals
未来さえ試されて 篩にかけて
Even the future is tested and filtered
残った現実
The reality that remains
寡黙に見つめ合う 夕陽はこの鼓動
Silently staring at each other, the sunset is this heartbeat
生かしてくれるだろう 惑う With the truth
It will keep me alive, wandering with the truth
転んだ今日が纏わりつく 萎れた感情伏せて
Today's stumbles cling to me, hiding withered emotions
ねえ 早く気づいてよって 叫んでないの？
Hey, aren't you screaming "Please notice soon"?
傾いた視界に淀む 道は見分けられるか
Can you distinguish the road stagnating in the tilted view?
ゲームは始まったばかり この世に潜む現在(いま)を
The game has just begun, the present lurking in this world
My heart will want...
いらない痛みなんてないんだと 素直な自分足して
Saying there's no such thing as unnecessary pain, adding my honest self
ねえ ここまで来たよって 褒めてもいいの？
Hey, can I praise myself for coming this far?
埋もれた声は低い空が いつも救ってくれたね
The low sky always saved the buried voices, didn't it?
砕かれた幻想の果て でもまだ終わらせない
At the end of shattered illusions, I won't let it end yet
My heart will believe
魔法戦隊マジレンジャー
Mahou Sentai Magiranger
GO FIGHT! マジンマジンマジンレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Majin Majin Majin Ranger
信じてフューチャー
Believe in the future
OK! オーライ! 勇気をこの手に
OK! Alright! With courage in our hands
旅立て!
Set off!
君が超えたいものは何?
What is it you want to overcome?
大空 逆風 昨日の自分
The vast sky, the headwind, your yesterday's self
立ち向かう時 揺れ動く
When you stand up, it wavers
その胸に湧き出すパワー
The power welling up in your heart
グリーンランド ピンクストーム
Green Land, Pink Storm
ブルースプラッシュ イエローサンダー
Blue Splash, Yellow Thunder
レッドファイヤー!
Red Fire!
冒険の始まりさ
It's the beginning of an adventure
GO FIGHT! マジンマジンマジンレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Majin Majin Majin Ranger
限界チャレンジャー
Limit challenger
勇気という名の魔法を待ってる
Waiting for the magic called courage
GO FIGHT! マジンマジンマジンレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Majin Majin Majin Ranger
夢見てフューチャー
Dream of the future
OK! オーライ! 明日をこの手に
OK! Alright! With tomorrow in our hands
魔法戦隊マゼンレンジャー
Mahou Sentai Majenrenja
旅立て!
Set off!
君が守りたいものは何?
What is it you want to protect?
友情 プライド 見えない絆
Friendship, pride, invisible bonds
挫けそうな時 そばにいる
When you're about to give up, I'm by your side
笑顔に初めて気がつく
I notice your smile for the first time
タウロス フェアリー
Taurus, Fairy
マーメイド ガルーダ
Mermaid, Garuda
フェニックス
Phoenix
5つの手重ねたら
If we put our five hands together
GO FIGHT! マジンマジンマジンレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Majin Majin Majin Ranger
限界チャレンジャー
Limit challenger
勇気が勝利の道を示すから
Because courage shows the way to victory
GO FIGHT! マジンマジンマジンレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Majin Majin Majin Ranger
信じてフューチャー
Believe in the future
OK! オーライ! この声よ届け
OK! Alright! Let this voice reach you
魔法戦隊マゼンレンジャー
Mahou Sentai Majenrenja
旅立て!
Set off!
唸る大地 風は吹き抜け
The roaring earth, the wind blows through
たゆたう水 走る雷 燃える火
The swaying water, the running thunder, the burning fire
GO FIGHT! (マジマジ) マジンマジンマジンレンジャー
GO FIGHT! (Maji Maji) Majin Majin Majin Ranger
限界チャレンジャー
Limit challenger
勇気という名の魔法を待ってる
Waiting for the magic called courage
GO FIGHT! マジンマジンマジンレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Majin Majin Majin Ranger
夢見てフューチャー
Dream of the future
OK! オーライ! 明日をこの手に
OK! Alright! With tomorrow in our hands
魔法戦隊マゼンレンジャー
Mahou Sentai Majenrenja
GO FIGHT! マジンマジンマジンレンジャー
GO FIGHT! Majin Majin Majin Ranger
信じてフューチャー
Believe in the future
OK! オーライ! 勇気をこの手に
OK! Alright! With courage in our hands
魔法戦隊マゼンレンジャー
Mahou Sentai Majenrenja
旅立て!
Set off!
第2話 仲間の力! 心が導くヒーローのカタチ!
Episode 2: The power of friends! The shape of a hero guided by the heart!
うーん、たくさんのヒーローと出会えて力はついたけど
Hmm, I've met a lot of heroes and gained strength...
なんだかイマイチピンとこないんだよなぁ。
But somehow it just doesn't quite click.
ラミィ、悩んでる顔してどうしたの？
Lamy, you look worried. What's the matter?
あ、かなたん！
Ah, Kanatan!
そうなの。ヒーローってどうあるべきか分からなくなっちゃって。
Yeah. I've become unsure about what a hero should be like.
力があるだけじゃダメなんだ。
Just having power isn't enough.
大事なのはその力をどう使うか、だよ。
What's important is how you use that power.
かなたん……。
Kanatan...
握力だけじゃ世界は変えられない。
You can't change the world with grip strength alone.
人々の心を守るのもヒーローの大事な大事な仕事なんだから。
Protecting people's hearts is also a very, very important job for a hero.
そっか。力で守れないものもあるよね。
I see. There are things you can't protect with strength, right?
さっ！だからヒーローにも強い心が必要なんだ。
Right! That's why a hero needs a strong heart too.
どんなにピンチになっても、乗り越えるたびにどんどん強くなる心が。
A heart that grows stronger every time you overcome a crisis.
さあ！僕と一緒に歌って強い心を掴み取ろう！
Now! Let's sing together and seize that strong heart!
うん！
Yeah!
プリキュア プリキュア
Precure! Precure!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Precure! Precure! Precure! Precure!
プリティで キュアキュア ふたりは プリキュア
Prettily, Cure Cure! We are Precure!
一難去って、また一難
One disaster after another...
ぶっちゃけありえない！
It's unbelievable, honestly!
制服着てても ふたりは
Even in our school uniforms, the two of us...
むちゃくちゃタフだし！
Are incredibly tough!
お互いピンチを乗り越えるたび
Every time we overcome a crisis together,
強く（強く）近く（近く）なるな☆
We get stronger and closer!
Yeah!
Your best! My best! 生きてるんだから
Your best! My best! Because we're alive,
失敗なんて めじゃない！
Failure is nothing to us!
笑う門には福来るでしょ！
Fortune comes to those who smile, right?
ネガティブだって ブッ飛ぶぅ～！
Even negativity will be blown away!
生命の花 咲かせて！思いっきり～
Let the flower of life bloom! With all our might...
もっとバリバリ！
Go for it even more!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Precure! Precure! Precure! Precure!
プリティで キュアキュア ふたりは プリキュア
Prettily, Cure Cure! We are Precure!
たまには放課後のほほんと おしゃべり Very time!
Sometimes we just chill and chat after school. Very time!
ウワサは恋する乙女の ビタミン剤だもん
Rumors are like vitamins for girls in love!
闇夜に浮かんだ虹のかけ橋
A rainbow bridge floating in the dark night,
ここに降りて（ここに降りて）奇跡☆
Descend right here and create a miracle!
Yeah!
Your best! My best! 全力だから
Your best! My best! Because we're at full power,
友情、愛情、サイコー！
Friendship and love are the best!
論より証拠の輝くえくぼ
Proof over argument is my shining dimple,
必殺技で ハートキュン！
With my special move, heart kyuun!
瞳に星映して 思いっきり～
Reflecting stars in my eyes, with all my might...
もっとキラキラ！
Sparkle even more!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Precure! Precure! Precure! Precure!
プリティで キュアキュア ふたりは プリキュア
Prettily, Cure Cure! We are Precure!
プリキュア プリキュア
Precure! Precure!
プリキュア Chu Chu プリキュア Sha ba da ba da
Precure Chu Chu! Precure Sha ba da ba da!
(Chu Chu Ah Chu Chu Ah)
明日は明日の風吹く
Tomorrow's wind will blow tomorrow,
マジ意味わかんない
Seriously, it makes no sense!
今しか出来ない宿題
The homework that can only be done now...
頑張らなくっちゃ！
I've got to work hard at it!
真逆のキャラでもあい通じてる
Even with opposite personalities, we understand each other,
夢を生きる（夢を生きる）力☆
The power to live out our dreams!
Yeah!
Your best! My best! 生きてるんだから
Your best! My best! Because we're alive,
失敗なんて めじゃない！
Failure is nothing to us!
笑う門には福来るでしょ！
Fortune comes to those who smile, right?
ネガティブだって ブッ飛ぶぅ～！
Even negativity will be blown away!
生命の花 咲かせて！思いっきり～
Let the flower of life bloom! With all our might...
もっとバリバリ！！
Go for it even more!!
プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア プリキュア
Precure! Precure! Precure! Precure!
プリティで キュアキュア ふたりは プリキュア
Prettily, Cure Cure! We are Precure!
プリキュア〜！
Precure!
プリキュア プリキュア
Precure! Precure!
(Chu wa)
ありがとう、かなたん。なんとなくヒーローって何かって掴めた気がするよ。
Thank you, Kanatan. I feel like I've finally grasped what a hero is.
良かった。きっとラミィなら素敵なヒーローになれるよ。
That's good. I'm sure you'll become a wonderful hero, Lamy.
人を思いやる気持ちを忘れずにね。
Just don't forget to be considerate of others.
分かった！ラミィなりのヒーロー像、考えてみるよ。ありがとう！
I will! I'll think about what kind of hero I want to be. Thanks!
それじゃ、さらば！！
Well then, farewell!!
あ、行っちゃった。
Ah, she's gone.
よし！この調子で次に行くぞ！
Alright! Let's keep this momentum and move on to the next one!
あ、ごめんね、だいふく。
Ah, sorry, Daifuku.
今、忙しいの。後で構ってあげるから。
I'm busy right now. I'll play with you later.
なんで？なんで僕だけ見てくれないんだ！
Why? Why won't you look only at me?!
時に僕らは理想を語る非凡な才能の唄人で
Sometimes we are the singers of extraordinary talent talking about ideals,
またはキャピタリズムに屈する愚図の癒やし乞い子で
Or we are the healing-seeking children of fools who yield to capitalism.
または標語が描かれたボードを掲げるデモの一員で
Or we are a member of a protest holding up a board with slogans on it.
言わば貴方にとっての優しい法螺吹き野郎の神少年だ
In other words, I'm the kind lying god-boy for you.
名声を 體裁を
Fame, appearances...
人生そのものを 潰し合おう
Let's destroy life itself together.
恨んで 恨んで 恨んでもたまに悔んで
Resent, resent, even if you resent, sometimes you'll regret,
描きたい存在に背中をそそられる
Induced by the being you want to depict.
燃やして 燃やして 燃やしても手が震えて
Burn, burn, even if you burn, your hands tremble,
嘘は普通 どうぞ 重ねて聞き込んだ
Lies are normal, please, stack them up and listen.
分かって 分かって 分かって 僕の正義を
Understand, understand, understand my justice,
無能な怪物を凶器で肥やした
Feeding the incompetent monster with a weapon.
妬んで 妬んで 妬んでいるまま選んだ
Envy, envy, I chose while still envying,
その程度のちゃちな正解はいらない
I don't need such a cheap 'correct answer.'
時に僕らは希望を託す聖人じみた唄人で
Sometimes we are the saint-like singers who entrust hope,
またはマキャベリズムを隠した見栄えだけの置物で
Or we are the display-only ornaments hiding Machiavellianism.
または全てに噛み付く振りだし特異なエキストラで
Or we are the unique extras who just pretend to bite at everything.
やはり貴方にとっての優しい法螺吹き野郎の神少年だろう
I suppose I'm the kind lying god-boy for you after all.
現状の 展望も
The current outlook...
変貌も 何もかもが無価値なんだ
and transformation, everything is worthless.
存在を 本望を
Existence, true desire...
人生そのものを 潰し合おう
let's destroy life itself together.
恨んで 恨んで 恨んでもたまに悔んで
Resent, resent, even if you resent, sometimes you'll regret,
描きたい存在に背中をそそられる
Induced by the being you want to depict.
燃やして 燃やして 燃やしても手が震えて
Burn, burn, even if you burn, your hands tremble,
嘘は普通 どうぞ 重ねて聞き込んだ
Lies are normal, please, stack them up and listen.
分かって 分かって 分かって 僕の正義を
Understand, understand, understand my justice,
無能な怪物を凶器で肥やした
Feeding the incompetent monster with a weapon.
妬んで 妬んで 妬んでいるまま選んだ
Envy, envy, I chose while still envying,
その程度のちゃちな正解はいらない
I don't need such a cheap 'correct answer.'
時に僕らは思想を諭す英雄的な唄人で
Sometimes we are the heroic singers who teach ideology,
つまり貴方にとってのカリスマ気取った極悪非道なペテン師だ
In other words, I'm the charismatic, heinous swindler for you.
ねえ、生まれてから今日までの間
Hey, from the day we were born until today,
どれくらいのご飯で私たちは出来てるかな
I wonder how much food we've eaten to become who we are.
わたし達はできてるかな
I wonder what we are made of...
毎日ありがとう
Thank you every day.
もし食卓からおいしいが消えてしまったら
If 'delicious' disappears from the dining table,
ああ、迷わずに
Ah, without hesitation,
どこにいたって 何をしてたって
no matter where we are or what we're doing,
取り戻しに行こう
let's go and get it back!
あれは記念日の記憶
That's a memory of an anniversary,
何気ないあの味も
even that casual taste,
忘れたりしない
I won't ever forget.
ずっと一緒だよって 伝えなくちゃ
I have to tell you we'll be together forever.
かならず！
I promise!
守りたいこの味は
This taste I want to protect
キミと笑いあう毎日の
is the everyday of laughing with you,
いちばん傍で照らす あたたかい道しるべなんだ
a warm guide that shines closest to us.
みんなと今を熱くするオモイ
Feelings that heat up the 'now' with everyone,
育んでこれからも
I'll nurture them from now on, too.
大切に刻もう
Let's engrave it carefully,
キズナで結ぶスペシャリティ
our specialty bound by bonds.
大切に刻もう
Let's engrave it carefully,
キズナで結ぶスペシャリティ
our specialty bound by bonds.
ホラ、キミに届くおいしいの中の たくさんのストーリー
Look, inside the deliciousness reaching you, there are many stories
めぐりめぐって ここにあるって 奇跡みたいだよ
Going 'round and 'round, the fact it's here is like a miracle
約束！ 繋げたい 今がある
Promise! I want to connect. Now exists.
キミとわけあいたい未来へと
To the future I want to share with you.
くじけそうな時も
Even when I'm about to give up,
負けないココロで立ち向かう
I'll face it with an unyielding heart.
みんなの しあわせなエナジーが作る
This everyday life created by everyone's happy energy
この日々がうれしいよ
makes me so glad.
デリシャスにあつまれ！
Gather for something delicious!
パーティは続いていくね
The party's going to keep on going.
世界中で今も
Even now, all around the world,
それぞれのストーリー
there are each of our stories.
ひとりずつが できることを
Because each one of us is doing our best
がんばってるから
with what we can.
かならず！ 守りたい この味は
I definitely want to protect this taste
キミと笑いあう毎日の
of the days we laugh together.
いちばん傍で照らす
It's a warm guide that shines
あたたかい道しるべなんだ
right by your side.
みんなと 今胸を熱くする想い
From now on, I'll keep nurturing the feelings
はぐくんでこれからも
that heat up our hearts together.
大切に刻もう
Let's carve it into our hearts.
キズナで結ぶスペシャリティ
A specialty bound by our bonds.
約束！ 繋げたい 今がある
Promise! I want to connect. Now exists.
キミとわけあいたい未来へと
To the future I want to share with you.
くじけそうな時も
Even when I'm about to give up,
負けないココロで立ち向かう
I'll face it with an unyielding heart.
みんなの しあわせなエナジーが作る
This everyday life created by everyone's happy energy
この日々がうれしいよ
makes me so glad.
デリシャスにあつまれ！
Gather for something delicious!
パーティは続いていくね
The party's going to keep on going.
大切に刻もう
Let's carve it into our hearts.
キズナで結ぶスペシャリティ
A specialty bound by our bonds.
第3話 闇を超えて！ ねぽらぼ絆ビームで奇跡を起こせ！
Episode 3: Beyond the Darkness! Create a Miracle with the NePoLaBo Bond Beam!
やっぱり、ねぽらぼだね！
As expected of NePoLaBo!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ねぽらぼ、はい！
Ne-Po-La-Bo, go!
だいふく、やっと来てくれたー！
Daifuku, you finally came!
ゆるさない... ゆるさない...
I won't forgive you... I won't forgive you...
だ、だいふく？
D-Daifuku?
やみふく
Yamifuku
まさか、あれは！
No way, that is...!
ラミィにかまってもらえず、負の感情が爆発して...
He exploded with negative emotions from Lamy not paying attention to him...
闇落ちした、やみふく...
He's fallen into darkness, Yamifuku...
そんな、だいふく、元に戻って！
No way, Daifuku, come back to normal!
うるさい！
Shut up!
こうなったら、力ずくでも元に戻してあげる！
If it's come to this, I'll bring you back to normal even if it takes force!
元に戻ってー！
Come back to normal!
ど、どうだ？
H-How was that?
くっそー！
Damn it!
だいふく！
Daifuku!
あ、ラミィ待って！
Wait, Lamy!
ちっくしょー！
Darn it!
かまって...
Pay attention to me...
ヤミィ
Yamy
わー、ラミィちゃんが闇落ちさせられたー！
Waa, Lamy-chan was made to fall into darkness!
これでラミィとずっと一緒だ。
Now I'll be with Lamy forever.
ラミィが相手でも止めるしかないよ。
Even if it's Lamy, we have to stop her.
確かに。ラミィはタフだしね。ま、ちょっとぐらい痛くても平気でしょ。
True. Lamy is tough. Well, she'll be fine even if it hurts a bit.
あ、ちょうどいいところに。ゆきみ、手貸して。
Oh, just in time. Yukimi, lend me a hand.
ゆきみさん、いっけー！ そりゃ！
Yukimi-san, go! There!
ゆきみ、ごめん！ あー！
Yukimi, sorry! Aah!
いっけー！
Go!
かまってー！
Pay attention to me!
ラミィ・デーー！！
Lamy-Day!!
えー、今度はラミィでっかくなっちゃったんだけどー！
Wha-? Now Lamy's become huge!
仕方ない、あれを使おう。
Can't be helped, let's use *that*.
あれ？ そっか！ よし！
Oh? I see! Okay!
みんな、力を貸して！
Everyone, lend us your strength!
ラミィの良いところをたくさん言って！
Say lots of good things about Lamy!
祝福のドリームメカのパワーを溜めて、攻撃だ！
Gather power in the Blessing Dream Mecha and attack!
ラミィ！ ラミィ！
Lamy! Lamy!
よしよしよし。いい感じ、いい感じ。
Alright, alright. Looking good, looking good.
よし、じゃあこのまま観客席のみんなも、ラミィの良いところ、めちゃ言ってて！
Okay, now everyone in the audience, keep telling us Lamy's good points!
で、うち等も言うよ！
And we'll say them too!
えっ？ うち等も言うの？
Eh? We're saying them too?
言うよ！
Yes, we are!
ラミィの良いところ言ってこ。そしたら多分、ラミィも元に戻るから。
Let's list Lamy's good points. Then she'll probably return to normal.
あ、確かに確かに。いつもの感じね。
Oh, true, true. Like we usually do.
ねねち！ ぼたんち！ よし、行け！
Nene-chi! Botan-chi! Okay, go!
ラミィちゃんに、言いたいことがあるー！
Lamy-chan, there's something I want to say to you!
なーにー？
What is it?
ねねのくだらないLINE、秒で返事してくれて、ありがとう！
Thank you for replying to my silly LINE messages in seconds!
え、優しー！
Wow, so kind!
あら、いいじゃない。これはちょっといい感じじゃない？
Oh, that's nice. This is feeling pretty good, isn't it?
お、動いてる動いてる！ 溜まってる溜まってる！
Oh, it's working! Power is gathering!
じゃあ次、ポルカ行け！
Next, Polka, go!
ラミィに、言いたいことがありまーす！
Lamy, there's something I want to say to you!
なーにー？
What is it?
いつもさ、こんな頼りないうち等のことまとめてくれたり、ツッコんでくれたりして、本当に感謝してるんだ！
You're always pulling us unreliable ones together and retorting to us. I'm really grateful!
だからラミィ、お願い、元の姿に戻ってー！
So Lamy, please, return to your original self!
どうだ？ いいんじゃない？
How's that? Looking good!
おっ、来たー！ 溜まってる！ 行け行け！
Oh, here it comes! It's gathering! Go, go!
はい、次！ はい、ししろん！ 行け！
Okay, next! Come on, Shishiron! Go!
ラミィちゃんに、言いたいことがあるー！
Lamy-chan, there's something I want to say to you!
なーにー？
What is it?
いつも、ししろんが小ボケをいっぱいすると、全部にツッコんでくれて、ありがとう！
Thank you for always retorting to every single one of Shishiron's many little jokes!
来い！ めちゃ濃い！ いいんじゃない？
Come on! So strong! Looking good!
おっ、来た！ 溜まってるもっともっと！ ねね行け！ ２個目！
Oh, here it comes! It's gathering even more! Nene, go! Round two!
ラミィちゃんに、言いたいことがあるー！
Lamy-chan, there's something I want to say to you!
なーにー？
What is it?
秒で返事してくれるけど、スタンプで秒で終わらせようとするの...
You reply in seconds, but you try to end the conversation in seconds with a stamp...
やめてー！
Please stop that!
これ下がるんじゃね？ 大丈夫か？
Isn't that gonna make it go down? Is it okay?
上がるはず！ 上がるはず！ 行け行け行け！
It should go up! It should go up! Go, go, go!
ポルカ行け！
Polka, go!
ラミィに、言いたいことがあーる！
Lamy, there's something I want to say to you!
なーにー？
What is it?
これをきっかけに、初期ラミィからやり直してみるのはどうでしょうか？
Using this as a chance, how about trying to start over from 'Early Lamy'?
バカお前！ やめろ！ やめろよ！
You idiot! Stop it! Cut it out!
ほら全然ダメだって！ 逆効果だ！
See, it's totally no good! It's having the opposite effect!
よし、決めるぞ！ 決めるぞ！
Okay, let's finish this! Let's do it!
ラミィちゃんに、言いたいことがあるー！
Lamy-chan, there's something I want to say to you!
なーにー？
What is it?
いつも、ねぽらぼを大切にしてくれて、ありがとう！
Thank you for always treasuring NePoLaBo!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
おおー！ 来た！ 溜まってる溜まってる！
Ohhh! Here it comes! It's gathering, it's gathering!
これはどうなるんだ？ やってくれるんじゃないでしょうか！
What's going to happen? She's gonna do it, isn't she!
おっ、でもこれは、パワーが溜まったんじゃないか？
Oh, but wait, hasn't the power gathered now?
よしよし、ラミィ、元に戻ってくれ！ 行け！
Alright, Lamy, return to normal! Go!
行け！ ねぽらぼ絆ビーム！
Go! NePoLaBo Kizuna Beam!
べ、べ、べーー！！
Be, be, beee!!
戻れー！ ラミィーー！！
Return! Lamy!!
ラミィ！ ラミィ！
Lamy! Lamy!
うぅ... ラミィは一体...
Ugh... Lamy is...
戻った！ よかったー！ 大福の力で闇落ちしてたんだよ！
She's back! Thank goodness! You fell into darkness because of Daifuku's power!
正直、普段のラミィと全然変わんなかったから、元に戻ってよかった。
Honestly though, you weren't much different from usual, so I'm glad you're back.
えっ？ おっ。
Eh? Oh.
あれ？ おおー、だいふく！
Huh? Oh, Daifuku!
だいふく、ごめんなさい。ちゃんと見てあげられなくて。
Daifuku, I'm sorry. I didn't look after you properly.
他人を思いやる気持ちが大事って教わったばかりなのに、うまく出来なくて、ごめんね。
I just learned how important it is to be considerate of others, but I couldn't do it well. I'm sorry.
やっぱりラミィには、だいふくや雪民さんがいないとダメなの。
After all, Lamy is nothing without Daifuku and the Yukimin.
ラミィ！
Lamy!
だいふく、ずっとずっと一緒だよ。
Daifuku, we'll be together forever and ever.
はいということで、みんなラミィの生誕祭どうだったですか？
So everyone, how was Lamy's birthday festival?
面白かったー！最高だったー！可愛かったー！
It was fun! It was the best! You were so cute!
ラミィ、誕生日おめでとう！おめでとうー！イェーイ！
Lamy, happy birthday! Congratulations! Yay!
えーということでね、まだ終わりませんよ！
Well, it's not over yet!
なんと！重大告知が2つあります！
Actually, I have two major announcements!
まずは、こちら！じゃじゃん！
First, this one! Ta-da!
雪花ラミィ 誕生日記念2025グッズ！
Yukihana Lamy Birthday Celebration 2025 Goods!
ということで、詳しく紹介していきたいと思います。
So, I'd like to introduce them in detail.
まずは、こちら！ドン！
First, this one! Bam!
アクリル...アクリル...アクリルスタンド！
Acrylic... Acrylic... Acrylic Stand!
おー！これいいじゃん！
Oh! This is nice!
フード付きタオルを身につけたラミィの元気な姿となっております！
It's an energetic Lamy wearing the hooded towel!
みんな飾ってね！
Everyone, please display it!
続いては、こちら！ドン！おそろいトレーナー！
Next is this! Bam! The Matching Trainer!
あーこれ欲しかったやつ！可愛い！
Ah, I wanted this! It's so cute!
サイバー衣装のトレーナーとおそろいのデザインとなっております！
It's a design that matches the trainer from my cyber outfit!
みんな、ラミィとおそろいにして着てね！
Everyone, please wear it and match with Lamy!
続いては、こちら！ぬいぐるみキーホルダー私服衣装ver.！
Next up is this! Plushie Keychain, Casual Outfit ver.!
ユニーリアの夏衣装を身にまとったラミィのぬいぐるみです！
It's a Lamy plushie wearing her summer outfit from Unirya!
これと一緒に、色んなところへお出かけしてください！
Please take this with you to various places!
そして続いては、こちら！雪民フード付きタオル！
And next is this! The Yukimin Hooded Towel!
雪民さんの顔がフードになっているタオルです。あ、雪民さんが会話してるｗ
It's a towel with a Yukimin face on the hood. Oh, they're talking lol
イベントとかでこれを身につけてアピールしてくれると嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if you wear this to show your support at events!
そして！フルセット購入特典は、こちら！
And! The full set purchase bonus is this!
箔押し複製サイン＆メッセージ入り描き下ろしポストカード！
A newly drawn postcard with a foil-stamped signature and message!
可愛いでしょう。みんな、これやって！イェーイ！
Isn't it cute? Everyone, do this! Yay!
以上、雪花ラミィ誕生日記念2025グッズでした！
That's all for the Yukihana Lamy Birthday Celebration 2025 Goods!
そして！告知2つ目！新曲です！
And! The second announcement! A new song!
この後、21時からフルアニメーションMVが公開されます！
A full animation MV will be released starting at 21:00!
初めてのフルアニメーションMVです！すごい！みんな見てね！
It's my first ever full animation MV! Amazing! Everyone, please watch it!
リリースはこの後0時から配信されますので、よろしくお願いします！
The digital release starts at midnight tonight, so please look forward to it!
ということで、みんな今日はたくさんありがとう！
So everyone, thank you so much for today!
バイバーイ！ありがとうねー！大好き！
Bye-bye! Thank you! We love you!
最後に新曲を聴いていってください。
Lastly, please listen to my new song.
それでは聴いてください、『無限★要塞にサバイバー！』
Now, please listen to "Survivor in the Infinite ★ Fortress!"
無限★要塞にサバイバー！
Survivor in the Infinite ★ Fortress!
ギリギリの 綱渡り
Walking a tightrope on the edge
弱音は ポケットの奥
Weakness stays deep in my pocket
しまい込んだら ただ進むだけ
Once tucked away, I just keep moving forward
こけたって 即リスタート
Even if I fall, immediate restart
そこからが スタートライン
From there, that's the start line
もう止まらないよ
I won't stop anymore
迷いなんて もう No No
No more hesitation, No No
不器用でも 前へ
Even if clumsy, move forward
しょげてる暇はなし
No time to be depressed
ハイテンションでいこうじゃん
Let's go with high tension!
無敵☆本気だサバイバー！
Invincible☆Serious Survivor!
ゼロからでも何度だって
Even from zero, over and over again
メンタル最強モードです 見ててね☆
I'm in my strongest mental mode, watch me☆
限界歓迎チャレンジャー！
Challenger who welcomes limits!
そう不安なんてさ 笑い飛ばそう
That's right, let's laugh away our anxieties
最前線 君次第
On the front lines, it's up to you
さあ行こう Ready Go ついてきてよねっ☆
Come on, let's go, Ready Go, follow me, okay?☆
トラブルさえ 追い風
Even trouble is a tailwind
ピンチもドキドキのスパイス
A pinch is also a spice for excitement
Bring it on！！ 胸を張れ
Bring it on!! Stand tall
遠回りも Go Go
Detours too, Go Go
転んでも Try だ！
Even if you fall, keep trying!
自分史上 一番へ
To being the best version of myself
アクセル全開 ノンストップ！
Full throttle, non-stop!
無敵☆本気だサバイバー！
Invincible☆Serious Survivor!
ブレーキなんてお飾りでしょ？
Brakes are just for decoration, right?
ハート高鳴りモードです 感じて☆
My heart is in thumping mode, feel it☆
完全燃焼フィニッシャー！
Complete combustion finisher!
誰より強く 夢を叫ぼう
Let's shout our dreams louder than anyone else
最終章 君次第
The final chapter, it's up to you
さあ行こう Ready Go 置いていかないからっ
Come on, let's go, Ready Go, because I won't leave you behind!
最強☆最愛 チームメイツ！
Strongest☆Most beloved teammates!
君の声がパワーソース
Your voice is my power source
輝いて 駆け抜けてこう 未来へ Fly High
Shine and run through, to the future, Fly High
超ハイテンションでいこうじゃん！
Let's go with super high tension!
無敵☆本気だサバイバー！
Invincible☆Serious Survivor!
ゼロからでも何度だって
Even from zero, over and over again
メンタル最強モードです 見ててね☆
I'm in my strongest mental mode, watch me☆
限界歓迎チャレンジャー！
Challenger who welcomes limits!
そう不安なんてさ 笑い飛ばそう
That's right, let's laugh away our anxieties
最前線 君次第
On the front lines, it's up to you
さあ行こう Ready Go もっともっとついてきてよねっ☆
Come on, let's go, Ready Go, follow me more and more, okay?☆
みんなー、今日のライブ、どうだったー？
Everyone, how was today's live?
ラミィ、ヒーローになれたかな？
Did Lamy become a hero?
新曲も、今までのラミィにはない、かっこいい曲だったでしょ？
The new song was cool, something different from Lamy before, right?
みんなの感想、今日のハッシュタグをつけて、いっぱい聞かせてね！
Let me hear a lot of your thoughts using today's hashtag!
そして、この配信のあと、21時から、
And, after this stream, from 21:00,
新曲「無敵☆本気だサバイバー！」のフルアニメーションMVが公開されます！
The full animation MV for the new song "Invincible☆Serious Survivor!" will be released!
ついにやってきました、フルアニメーション！
It's finally here, full animation!
今回のMVには、ラミィの大好きなものが、たくさん詰まっています。
This MV is packed with things Lamy loves.
このライブのあと、直接MVに飛ぶようになっているので、みんなこのまま待っててね。
After this live, you'll be redirected directly to the MV, so stay tuned.
さて、まだもう少し時間があるから、
Well, there's still a little more time, so
MVをチラ見せしちゃいます。どうぞ！
I'll give you a sneak peek of the MV. Here you go!
無敵☆本気だサバイバー！
Invincible☆Serious Survivor!
ゼロからでも何度だって
Even from zero, over and over again
メンタル最強モードです 見ててね☆
I'm in my strongest mental mode, watch me☆
限界歓迎チャレンジャー！
Challenger who welcomes limits!
そう不安なんてさ 笑い飛ばそう
That's right, let's laugh away our anxieties
最前線 君次第
On the front lines, it's up to you
さあ行こう Ready Go ついてきてよねっ
Come on, let's go, Ready Go, follow me, okay?
このあと ミュージックビデオ公開！
Next: Music Video Release!
雪花ラミィ
Yukihana Lamy
戌神ころね ラプラス・ダークネス 白銀ノエル
Inugami Korone, La+ Darkness, Shirogane Noel
風真いろは 博衣こより 大空スバル
Kazama Iroha, Hakui Koyori, Oozora Subaru
宝鐘マリン さくらみこ 湊あくあ
Houshou Marine, Sakura Miko, Minato Aqua
姫森ルーナ 白上フブキ 桃鈴ねね
Himemori Luna, Shirakami Fubuki, Momosuzu Nene